gov.je 2019-05-03

# Privacy policy

## Your personal information and what we collect

We do not capture or store any personal information about you when you access our website, except where you voluntarily choose to give us your personal details by:

  * email
  * using an electronic form
  * enquiring about any of our services
  * signing up to gov.je, our [one.gov.je service](https://one.gov.je/login?return_url=https://one.gov.je/en&lang=en&appName=Self&_ga=2.51010602.2029928142.1526891747-2114549670.1513590211), our customs clearance service [CAESAR](https://www.customs.gst.gov.je/?_ga=2.51010602.2029928142.1526891747-2114549670.1513590211) or our job application site Talentlink

## What we do with the information we gather 

### When you sign up for our services

We store your contact information to understand your needs and provide you with a personalised service. 

We do not share the information you provide with any third parties and we protect it in accordance with the [Data Protection (Jersey) Law 2018.](https://www.jerseylaw.je/laws/enacted/Pages/L-03-2018.aspx)

### When you contact us

If you contact us asking for information, we may need to send your enquiry to other government departments in order to respond to your request.

### When you sign up for email subscriptions

Some areas of this website offer email updates. To receive these email updates, you need to register by giving: 

  * your email address
  * a user name
  * a password

We do not share the information you provide with any third parties and we protect it in accordance with the [Data Protection (Jersey) Law 2018.](https://www.jerseylaw.je/laws/enacted/Pages/L-03-2018.aspx)

## Cookies

We use cookies on our website. Cookies are small files which can be stored on your computer when you visit a website. These files contain information about the webpages you look at so that the next time you visit the site it can be customised to meet your needs. 

Read our Cookies policy to find out more.

## Links to other websites

Links on our website may lead to other websites which are not under our control. Using these links does not mean these organisations can access information about you which is held by the States of Jersey.

This privacy policy only covers the States of Jersey website (www.gov.je). Websites linked to, and from, this site are not covered by this policy so you should always read the privacy statement on that website.

The States of Jersey is not responsible for the content of external websites.

## Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to help us understand how you engage with our website so that we can continually improve your experience. 

When you visit gov.je your browser automatically sends certain information to Google. This includes, for example, the web address of the page that you're visiting and your IP address.

[Learn how to control the information your browser sends to Google on Google's website](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)

## IP address

Your computer’s IP address is a number assigned to your computer when you use the internet. This is recorded automatically in a log file when you visit our site. This log file does not contain any personal identifiable information about you.

## The Data Protection Law

We comply with the [Data Protection (Jersey) Law 2018](https://www.jerseylaw.je/laws/enacted/Pages/L-03-2018.aspx), and the good practice for the handling of personal data contained within that act.

Information we collect about you will not be disclosed to any third party without your prior consent or the requestor's demonstrated legal authority to receive it.

## Changes to this policy

We may, at any time, revise this privacy statement without notice so you should check it regularly. Continued use of the States of Jersey website after a change has been made is your acceptance of the change.
